octablogs.com 2009-06-02

# Octablogs: Privacy Policy

Octablogs.com (“Octablogs”) takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting the Octablogs website (the “Octablogs Site”), submitting information or using any of our services, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy.

##  What Does This Privacy Policy Cover? 

This Privacy Policy covers Octablogs treatment of personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) that this site gathers when you are accessing the Octablogs Site and when you use our services or register for events provided by Octablogs. Also, this Privacy Policy covers Octablogs treatment of any Personal Information that our valued business partners share with Octablogs. This Privacy Policy is not applicable to the practices of companies that Octablogs does not own or control, or to individuals that Octablogs does not employ or manage.

##  What Personal Information Does Octablogs Collect and Use? 

  * Web Site collects personal information when you register with Octablogs , when you use the Octablogs services, and when you visit Octablogs pages or the pages of certain Octablogs partners. Octablogs may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.
  * When you register we ask for information such as include your full name, website URL, e-mail address, blog or other personal website URL, your nickname or screen name, and any other information that would allow Octablogs to identify you or contact you if needed. Once you register with Octablogs and sign in to the Octablogs services, you are not anonymous to us.
  * Octablogs collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners. 
  * We may receive and store any information you enter on the Octablogs Site or provide to us in any other way. The Personal Information you provide may be used for providing attribution to comments you post, to operate and improve the Octablogs Site, and to better deliver the our services. 

##  Information Collected Automatically 

We may receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with our websites or services. Octablogs may choose to automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, Octablogs cookie information, and the page you requested. 

Octablogs uses “cookies” to collect non-personal data and information. Cookies are small text files a website uses to recognize repeat users, and is typically placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies contain information that can later be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. The way cookies function is by assigning a number to the user that has no meaning outside of the assigning Web site.

You should be aware that Octablogs cannot control the use of cookies (or the resulting information) by Octablogs third-party partners or advertisers. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to sign in or use other interactive features of Octablogs sites and services that depend on cookies.

##  Sharing of Personal Information 

Except as described in this Privacy Notice, your personal information will be used only by Octablogs and its controlled subsidiaries and affiliates, and your personal information will not be disclosed to any other third party without your consent. We share your Personal Information only with your consent or as described below: 

Agents: We may employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you. Unless we tell you differently, Octablogs agents do not have any right to use Personal Information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us. You hereby consent to our sharing of Personal Information for the above purposes. 

Business Transfers: In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Moreover, if Octablogs, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Octablogs may continue to use your Personal Information as set forth in this policy.

Protection of Octablogs and Others: We may release Personal Information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with any law; enforce or apply our terms of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Octablogs, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. 

**Confidentiality and Security**

We maintain reasonable standards of security and confidentiality and store Personal Information collected in a database. However, while we employ reasonable standards of security, no security system is impenetrable. For most internet sites, it is possible that third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions you transmit. As such, Octablogs cannot guarantee the security of our database, nor can we guarantee that information you supply won’t be intercepted while being transmitted to Octablogs over the internet. We recommend that you do not disclose your password or confirmation number (as applicable) to anyone.

##  Changes to this Privacy Policy 

Octablogs retains the discretion to amend or modify this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is collected. If we make changes in the way we use Personal Information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on the Octablogs Site, and such changes shall be effective immediately upon posting. You agree to review this Privacy Policy periodically to ensure that you are aware of any changes. Your continued access or use of the website and/or the services shall be deemed your conclusive acceptance of any amendments and/or modifications.

##  Questions or Suggestions Regarding this Privacy Policy 

Octablogs welcomes any questions or comments you may have regarding this Privacy Policy. If you have any, please [contact us](http://www.octablogs.com/contactus.php). 

**Effective Date of this Privacy Policy**
